난 다음 단계에 있어 그래
I’m on the Next Level Yeah
절대적인 규칙을 따르세요
I follow the absolute rules
내 손을 놓지 말아요 단결이 나의 무기예요
Don't let go of my hand, unity is my weapon
광야방향
I walk to KWANGYA
나는 너의 홈그라운드를 알고 있다
I know your Home ground
위협에 직면하세요. 그것을 패배시키세요.
Confront the threat, beat it, beat it, beat it
상상할 수 없는 Black out 유혹은 심연과 같아
An unexpected Black out, the temptation is deep and strong
꼭 잡은 손이 그리워 절대 포기하지 않아
Letting go of the hands held together, but I'll never give up
나는 다음 단계에 있다
I’m on the Next Level
멀리 있는 문을 열어라
I open the door over there
다음 레벨 당신
Next Level, I'll
나에 의해 파괴될 것이다
Destroy you in the end
다음 단계에 도달할 때까지 KOSMO
Until I reach the Next Level KOSMO
다음 레벨 이겨내자.
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
라라라라라라
La la la la la la
라라라라라
La la la la la
NU EVO가 보입니다.
I see the NU EVO.
적대감 고통과 고통
The hostile suffering and sorrow
당신을 더욱 톡톡 튀게 만들어줄
Make you Popping and evolve further
그게 내 네비스야 내 네비스야
That’s my nævis It’s my nævis
네가 이끄는 우리는 따라가는 마음을 배운 뒤
You lead, we follow, after learning the feelings
내가 정리하는 동안 지켜봐줘
Watch me while I make it out
내가 해결하는 동안 지켜봐줘
Watch me while I work it out
내가 정리하는 동안 지켜봐줘
Watch me while I make it out
내가 해결하는 동안 지켜봐줘
Watch me while I work it out
일해라 일해라 일해라
Work it work it work it out
참을 수 없는 절망
Even the unbearable despair
내 믿음을 깰 수 없어
Can't break my faith
더 고통스러운 시험을 만나도
Even if a more painful trial comes
나도 꼭 잡은 손을 놓지 않을 거야 Oh
I won't let go of your hand Oh
절대 뒤돌아보지 마세요
Never look back
KWANGYA의 모든 것을 탐내지 마세요
Don’t covet things of KWANGYA
계약이 파기되면 모든 것이 통제 불능이 됩니다
If the promises are broken, everything will be out of control
언제부터 불안해지기 시작했는지 모르겠어요.
The signal is becoming unstable since a certain point in time
나는 당신을 파괴해야합니다
I'll destroy you in the end
어서 코스모로 가는 길을 보여줘 Yeah
Come on! Show me the way to KOSMO Yeah
Black Mamba가 만든 환각 미션
A hallucination quest created by the Black Mamba
에스파, 에를 떼어놓고 싶어
aespa, They want to separate out ae, that’s right
집중력 상실, 목소리 상실
I lose my balance and my voice too
비난을 받아 사람들과 멀어진다는 착각 속에
In the illusion of being criticized and alienated
nævis us (ae, ae로 전화해 보세요)
nævis We (Call ae, ae)
aespa의 Next Level "P.O.S"를 활성화해 보세요.
aespa's Next Level Open "P.O.S"
현실 세계가 깨어난다
This is the REAL WORLD, I'm awake
우리는 악당에 맞서
We against the villain
이름은 무엇입니까?
What’s the name?
블랙 맘바
Black Mamba
드디어 내가 문을 열었어
I open the door in the end
그 빛은 너에게 Fire야
That light is like Fire to you
너무 궁금해서 미칠 것 같아
I'm dying to know
다가오는 이야기
The next Story that will unfold
뭐!
Huh!
나는 다음 단계에 있다
I’m on the Next Level
멀리 있는 문을 열어라
I open the door over there
다음 레벨 당신
Next Level, I'll
나에 의해 파괴될 것이다
Destroy you in the end
다음 단계에 도달할 때까지 KOSMO
Until I reach the Next Level KOSMO
다음 레벨 이겨내자.
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
나는 다음 단계에 있다
I’m on the Next Level
더 강하고 더 자유롭게
I become stronger and free
다음 레벨 나
Next Level, I'm
나는 광야가 아니다
No longer who I was at KWANGYA
다음 레벨 나를 짐승처럼 느껴보세요
Next Level, Feel me I'm like a beast
다음 레벨 이겨내자.
Next Level, beat it, beat it, beat it
뭐!
Huh!